Guide to the United Steelworkers of America Local 1843 Records, 1937-1999 AIS.2000.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Steelworkers of America Local 1843 Records
1937-1999
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Steelworkers of America. Local 1843 (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
AIS.2000.05
97.5 Linear Feet (78 boxes)
United Steelworkers of America, Local 1843 was founded in 1937 and represented workers at the Jones & Laughlin Steel mill in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. This collection includes seniority lists, agreements, membership cards and negotiation information from Local 1843.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Vincent Mackewich, president of Local 1843, in 2000.
History
United Steelworkers of America, Local 1843 was founded in 1937 as part of the Steelworkers Organizing Committee and represented workers at the Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation mill in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. The union continued to represent workers at the plant after it became part of LTV Steel and up to the plant's closure in 1999.
Previous Citation
United Steelworkers of America Local 1843 Records, 1937-1999, AIS.2000.05, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Related Material
Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation, Pittsburgh Works Earning Records, 1862-1901, AIS.1974.23, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation Historical Records, 1871-1953, AIS.1973.07, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation Records, 1902-1959, AIS.1978.09, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation, Pittsburgh Works Records, 1918-1970, AIS.1988.07, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Scope and Content Notes
This collection includes seniority lists, agreements, and negotiation information of United Steelworkers Local 1843 at the Jones & Laughlin steel mill on the South Side (Pittsburgh) and Hazelwood. Also present are membership cards from 1937 to 1954, arbitration information and grievances.
Iron and steel workers -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Steel industry and trade -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Membership cards; South Side (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Minute books; Hazelwood (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Iron and steel workers -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Labor; LTV Steel Company; Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation. Pittsburgh Works; United Steelworkers of America. Local 1843 (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
- Minute Books and Sign-In Book, 1976-1995 (Microfilm-cabinet 3, Reel 1-2)
- Vendor Blanket Orders, Day to Day Purchases, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Zone 1 Seniority, April 15, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- "Preventing Chemical Disasters: A Course for Safety and Health Committees" by the USWA Safety and Health Department, November 14-18, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Standard Proceedure Booklets (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Meetings, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Letters of Understanding, SUB SVP Working Agreement, August 1, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Craft and Maintenance Agreement, December 1, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Trade or Craft Apprenticeship (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Trade or Craft Agreement, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Zone 1 Agreement, 1946, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Contracts, 1968, 1986, 1999 (Box 3)
- Conventions, 1950-1972 (Box 3)
- Production Planning (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Food Service, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Strip Mill, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Closed Cases, 1960-1967 (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
- Arbitration Award, Appendix F Agreement, August 1, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Strip Mill Mechanical Units, Job Descriptions and Classifications, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
- Zone 2, Eliza Job Descriptions and Classifications (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
- Zone 3, Number 18 Mill Job Descriptions and Classifications (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Zone 3, Number 19 Mill Job Descriptions and Classifications (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1979-1982, 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Job Evaluations: Factors (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Letters of Agreement and Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Grievance Settlements, 1980-1986 (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
- Steel Workers Handbook on Arbitration Decisions (Box 6, Item 1)
- Labor-Management Arbitration Manual (Box 6, Item 2)
- Cradle of Steel Unionism, Monongahela Valley, PA (Box 6, Item 3)
- United Steelworkers of America 24th Constitutional Convention, August 1-5, 1988 (Box 6, Item 4)
- Zone 3A, Turning Department Incentive Plan (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Zone 3A, Bar Side Incentive Plan (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Zone 4, Incentives (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Zone 5, Anneal and Temper Mill Aisle Incentive Plan (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Zone 5B Incentive Plan (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Zone 5 Incentives (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Local 1843 Negotiations, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Local Union Issues, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Financial Officer's Manual (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Labor-Management Participation Teams Reference Manual (Box 8, Folder 4-6)
- Pittsburgh Works Occupations Affected by Craft and Maintenance Agreement, December 1, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Local 1843 Agreements, Zones 1, 2, 3 and 3A (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Trade or Craft Supplemental Agreements, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Contracting Out, 1979-1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Overtime Information, Zones 2-4 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Zone 3A, Coil Department and Incentives (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
- Zone 5A, Soho Galvanizing (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Zone 5A (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Zone 2, Foundry (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Zone 5, Roll Grinders (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Zone 5B (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Incentive Performances, 1970-1980 (Box 11, Folder 2-6)
- Contract Negotiations, 1947-1965 (Box 12)
- Contract Tape, 1994 (Box 13, Item 1)
- Crane 314 Furnace Room (Box 13, Item 2)
- Buttons (Box 13, Item 3)
- Blank Complaint Interview Notebooks (Box 13, Item 4)
- Complaint/Grievance Pamphlet (Box 13, Item 5)
- Blank Health, Safety and Environment Complaint Book (Box 13, Item 6)
- Pension, McDonald, January 20, 1991 (Box 13, Item 7)
- Negotiation Tapes, 1990 (Box 13, Item 8)
- Third Step Grievance Hearings, April 7, 1976 (Box 13, Reel 1)
- Local 1843, Files of President Joseph Audia, 1950s (Box 14)
- Local 1843 Grievance Files, 1967-1979 (Box 15)
- Consent Decree Implementation, Locals 1843 and 1272, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Consent Decree, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Vacation Agreements and Letters (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Labor Pool, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Appendix F, Agreement Incentives, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Grievance Status Files (Box 17)
- Planners, Constitutions, Agreements and Programs (Box 18)
- Zone 1 Incentive Plan (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
- Zone 2 Incentive Plan (Box 19, Folder 3-4)
- Zone 3 Incentive Plan (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Zone 5, Pickle Lines Tandem Mill Incentive Plan (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Surfaglaze Department Incentive Plan (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Zone 3 Incentive Plan (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Zone 3, Incentives (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Zone 3A, Bar Department Incentive Plan (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Zone 3A Incentive Plan (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Zone 3A, Furnace Department Incentive Plan (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Zone 1, Overtime Agreements (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Labor Pool Agreement, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Incentive Plan Results, 1994-1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Manning Agreement and Job Descriptions, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Zone 1 by Product, 1950s, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Agreements, March 1, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Seniority, Zones 3, 4, 5A, 5B and 5 (Box 22, Folder 2-6)
- Clerical and Technical Job Classification Program (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Agreement: LTV Steel, Pittsburgh Works, Industrial Nurse Employees and the United Steelworkers of America, August 6, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- LTV Steel Coke Oven Battery Inspection, March-June 1997 (Box 23, Folder 3-5)
- Pension Agreement between Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation (and Union Dock Company) and United Steelworkers of America, January 1, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Pension Agreement between Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation (and Union Dock Company) and United Steelworkers of America, July 31, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Program of Insurance Benefits for Hourly Paid Employees of Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation Pursuant to Agreement with United Steelworkers of America, January 1, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Seniority, Zones 1-5B (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Local Collective Bargaining Issues, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Letters of Agreement, 1979-1990 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Consent Decree, Trane and Craft: Goals and Time Tables (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Joint Review Committee Rules of Procedure, Consent Decree, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Expedited Arbitration, 1970s (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Local Issues, January 23, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Contract Negotiations, 1980, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
- Quarterly Income Benefit, 1980s-1990s (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Labor-Management Participation Teams Manuals (Box 25, Item 1)
- Strip Sheet Department: New, Terminated and Retained Maintenance Jobs (Box 25, Item 2)
- Zone 3A, Hazelwood Cold Finishing Mill Job Descriptions and Classifications (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Zone 4, Hot Mill Job Descriptions and Classifications (Box 26, Folder 2-3)
- Zone 5A, Soho Galvanizing Job Descriptions and Classifications (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Zone 5, Cold Mill Job Descriptions and Classifications (Box 26, Folder 5-6)
- Bonus and Base Rate Incentive Plans by Zone (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
- LTV Steel/USWA Benefits Seminar, October 22-23, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Incentive Calculations by Zone (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
- Incentive Performances (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Zone 1 Seniority (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Contract Settlement, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Meetings, Local Joint Unions, 1970-1980 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Contract, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Negotiated Contract, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Arbitration (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Settlement Agreement, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Supplemental Master Job Classifications, August 1, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Arbitration Award Appendix F, Agreement Book 2, August 1, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Incentive Illustrations (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Incentive Information, Special Meetings, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- O&T Manual, Clerical and Technical Job Classifications, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 5-6)
- Conventions and Special Meetings by Zone, 1960s-1980s (Box 30)
- O&T Manual, Clerical and Technical Job Classifications (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Contract Negotiations, 1968, 1971, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 2-4)
- Contracts, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Agreements, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Local Issues, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Requests for Vacation Benefits, 1960s-1970s (Box 32)
- Grievances by Zone (Box 33)
- Job Progressions (Box 33)
- Job Lines and Seniorities (Box 33)
- Correspondence, Zone 5, 5A and 5B (Box 34)
- Incentive Population Report, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Hot Strip Mill Finishing Shutdown of B.A. Floor, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Incentive Evaluations, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 3-4)
- Job Lines and Seniorities (Box 36)
- Arbitrations and Settlements, 1960s-1970s (Box 37)
- Arbitrations, 1966-1967, 1969 (Box 38)
- Recovery Operations by Product, Zone 1 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Coil Side All Units (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Turning Department Cutoff, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Shipping and Finished Warehousing (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Letters of Suspension and Reprimand, 1980-1981 (Box 39, Folder 5-6)
- Recording Secretary Jerry King Files, 1970s, 1990s (Box 40)
- United Steelworkers of America 20th Constitutional Convention, August 5-8, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Industrial Nurses, 1971-1974 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Pension Agreements, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Arbitrations, 1980s (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Meeting Minutes, 1990s (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Zone 1-3, 1985-1987 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Hearing Recordings, 1970s (Box 42-43)
- Recordings of Grievances by Product, 1970s (Box 44)
- Special Meetings, 1970s (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Contract Comparison, August 1, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Consent Order (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Job Classification Manual, 1940s (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Local 1843 Case No. NS 1-72, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Check Book, 1980s (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Shutdown Arbitration, 1990s (Box 46)
- Expedited Arbitration, 1970s (Box 47)
- Contracts, Notes and 3rd Step Hearing Tapes, 1970s (Box 48)
- Correspondence, Zones 1-4 (Box 49)
- Coke Ovens, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Hazelwood Cold Finishing, 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Arbitration Decisions, Incentive Arbitration Award, August 1, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 3-4)
- Contracting Out, 1977-1979 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Consent Decree, 1970s (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Special Meetings by Zone, 1960s, 1980s (Box 51)
- Strikes, 1950s-1960s (Box 52)
- 3rd Step Grievances, 1984-1989 (Box 53)
- Agreements and Job Descriptions, 1950s-1970s (Box 54)
- Agreements, Zones 4, 5, 5A and 5B, 1950s-1960s (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Trade Readjustment Assistance, Suitable Lont Term Employment, 1970s-1980s (Box 55, Folder 2)
- LTV Steel Agreement, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- 3rd Step Grievances and Closed Cases, 1980 (Box 56)
- Case Studies, 4th and 5th Steps, 1970s-1980s (Box 57)
- Shutdown Arbitration, Pat Carvale (Box 58)
- Grievances, 1958, 1960, 1969, 1973 (Box 59)
- Grievance Settlements (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Labor Pool, 1966, 1993-1994, 1996-1997 (Box 60, Folder 2-3)
- Living Wage, Pat Carvale, 1990s (Box 61)
- Grievances, 1964-1965, 1979 (Box 62)
- National Labor Relations Board Cases (Box 63)
- Locals 1843 and 1272, Memorandum of Procedure being Followed at the Pittsburgh Works regarding Seniority, 1940 (Box 64, Item 1)
- Consent Decree I, April 12, 1974 (Box 64, Item 2)
- Local 1843 Labor Pool Agreement, 1966 (Box 64, Item 3)
- Local 1843 Award of Arbitration Panel on Appendix F of Agreement, August 1, 1968 (Box 64, Item 4)
- Affirmative Action Compliance Program for Equal Employment Opportunity, Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation (Box 64, Item 5)
- Supplemental Agreement Implementing Appendix G, Trade or Craft Memorandum of Understanding, Basic Labor Agreement, September 1, 1965 (Box 64, Item 6)
- Your Social Security Benefits, 1963, 1982 (Box 64, Item 7-8)
- Blue Cross, Blue Shield and Major Medical Handbook for Steel Pensioners (Box 64, Item 9)
- LTV Group Insurance, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Pension Benefit Guaranty Corporation Bankruptcy Decision, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Jobs to Bid, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Trade and Craft Jobs, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Craft Postings, April 1987 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Seniority, By Product, February 1987 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- LTV Pittsburgh Works Case Study (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Ed Kern (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Brief on Snapback of Pensions, July 23, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Asset Control, November 17, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Local Issues (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Dependent Enrollment Guide Lines, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- LTV Paradigm Shift (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Work System (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Dental Pre-Paid Plan Coverage and Amounts (Box 64, Folder 16)
- Company Information on Projects and Plant Studies, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Petitions Received, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Bankruptcy Information, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- Assistant Committeeman Meetings, 1991-1993 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- Summer Hires (Box 64, Folder 21)
- Labor-Management Participation Teams Training and Information, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 22)
- Local 1843 Steelworkers Food Fund Bank Charitable Trust, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 23)
- Inflation Recognition Payment, Quarterly Update Information, April 15, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 24)
- HMO Information, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 25)
- List of Employees Company is No Longer Witholding Wage Tax, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 26)
- Dennis Adair (Box 64, Folder 27)
- Incentive Plan Information (Box 64, Folder 28)
- J&L/LTV Industrial Police Association Information and Arbitration, Genesta St. Gate Closing, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 29)
- Bill McCray Daylight Bump, Ovens Operating Group (Box 64, Folder 30)
- Reprimands and Suspensions to Have Records Cleared (Box 64, Folder 31)
- Gate Closing, Hazelwood/Genesta St. Gate, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 32)
- Report of LTV Steel to USWA regarding Bankruptcy, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 33)
- Pension Examples, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 34)
- Chapter 11 Bankruptcy (Box 64, Folder 35)
- Overtime Agreements (Box 64, Folder 36)
- Zone 3A, Coil Drawing Job Line of Progression (Box 64, Folder 37)
- Zone 3A, Bar Subdivision Job Line of Progression (Box 64, Folder 38)
- Zone 4, Roll Shop Job Line of Progression (Box 64, Folder 39)
- Zone 4, Plate Finishing Seniority Unit Job Line of Progression (Box 64, Folder 40)
- Zone 4, Accounting Job Line of Progression (Box 64, Folder 41)
- Zone 5A, Spike Factory Job Line of Progression (Box 64, Folder 42)
- Zone 5B, Cold Reducing Job Line of Progression (Box 64, Folder 43)
- Zone 5B, Maintenance Job Line of Progression (Box 64, Folder 44)
- Engine Crew and Recovery Operations Incentives (Box 64, Folder 45-46)
- Zone 3, Production Stocker Helper-Burner Incentives (Box 64, Folder 47)
- Zone 3, Maintenance Welder Incentives (Box 64, Folder 48)
- Zone 3, Maintenance Grinder, Shearknife and Guide Incentives (Box 64, Folder 49)
- Hot Strip Mill Incentives (Box 64, Folder 50)
- Zone 3, 14 Inch Bar Mill Incentives (Box 64, Folder 51)
- Zone 5, Surfaglaze Polishing Line Incentives (Box 64, Folder 52)
- Zone 5A, Stainless Steel Grinders Incentives (Box 64, Folder 53-54)
- Zone 3, 10 Inch Bar Mill Incentives (Box 64, Folder 55)
- Zone 5B, Old Anneal Incentives (Box 64, Folder 56-57)
- Grievance Status (Box 64, Folder 58)
- Arbitration (Box 64, Folder 59)
- Changed Jobs (Box 64, Folder 60)
- Incentives (Box 64, Folder 61)
- New Jobs (Box 64, Folder 62)
- Special Meeting Requests (Box 64, Folder 63)
- Procedures (Box 64, Folder 64)
- Rates of Pay (Box 64, Folder 65)
- Seniorities (Box 64, Folder 66)
- Negotiations (Box 64, Folder 67)
- Scarfing (Box 64, Folder 68)
- Letters (Box 64, Folder 69-71)
- Expedited Arbitrations, 1993-1997 (Box 65-66)
- Arbitrations from Various Jones & Laughlin Locals, 1970s-1980s (Box 67)
- Grievance and Complaint Settlements, 1977-1999 (Box 68)
- USWA Local 1272 Settled Cases, 1981-1983 (Box 69-70)
- Local 1843 Settled Cases, 1982-1993 (Box 71)
- Constitution of the United Steelworkers of America, 1956, 1958, 1976, 1984 (Box 72, Item 1-4)
- Regulations Governing Working Conditions for Employees in the Motive Power Department Negotiated between the Monongahela Connecting Railroad Company and United Steelworkers of America, November 1, 1945 (Box 72, Item 5)
- Agreement between Bethlehem Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, April 30, 1947 (Box 72, Item 6)
- Agreement Relating to Insurance and Pensions and Supplemental Insurance Agreement between Superior Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Local 171, November 26, 1949 (Box 72, Item 7)
- Agreement between United States Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Production and Maintenance Employees, 1956, 1960 (Box 72, Item 8-9)
- Agreement between United States Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Salaried Employees, 1956, 1968 (Box 72, Item 10-11)
- Agreement between Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1977, 1980 (Box 72, Item 12-13)
- Consent Decree I, April 12, 1974 (Box 72, Item 14)
- Local 1843 Award of Arbitration Panel on Appendix F of Agreement, August 1, 1968 (Box 72, Item 15)
- Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation, 1969, 1974, 1977 (Box 72, Item 16-18)
- Program of Hospital-Medical Benefits for Eligible Pensioners and Surviving Spouses of Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation, 1983 (Box 72, Item 19)
- Pension Agreement between Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, July 31, 1969 (Box 72, Item 20)
- Savings and Vacation Plan, 1969 (Box 72, Item 21)
- An Explanation of the Employment and Income Security Program by USWA (Box 72, Item 22)
- Steel by USWA, 1980 (Box 72, Item 23)
- Georgetown Steel (Box 72, Item 24)
- KORF, German Steel Company (Box 72, Item 25)
- Swindell-Dressler, Electric Arc Furnaces (Box 72, Item 26)
- US Steel News, Why Are America's Steel Plants Closing?, July 1982 (Box 72, Item 27)
- Business Week, June 14, 1982 (Box 72, Item 28)
- Officers' Report by USWA, 21st Constitutional Convention, September 20-24, 1982 (Box 72, Item 29)
- Labor Pools and Correspondence, 1959-1971 (Box 72-73)
- Expediated Arbitration, 1997-1998 (Box 74)
- Arbitration and Grievances, 1987-1990 (Box 75)
- Minute Books and Sign-In Book, 1976-1995 (Box 76)
- Member Cards, 1937-1954 (Box 77-78)
- Dues Card, Badge and Poster, 1. (Map-case 3, Drawer 14)
- Inaugural Address of John Fitzgerald Kennedy, President of the United States, Given to Local 1843, January 20, 1961; 2.